Hey, what's up?
I left my guitar here again.
Oh, okay, no problem.
Okay.
Okay. Here you go.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Okay, uh...
What?
So you want to hang out
or something?
Phoebe, y-y-you kind of
caught me at a bad time.
Oh, are you and Chandler...?
Yes, exactly.
Okay.
Do you guys want me
to play for you?
No.
Hey, Pheebs, what's up?
You're asking an intriguing
question, Chandler Bing.
( gasps )
Oh, my God! You're
getting a massage?
You never let me massage you.
Phoebe, I can explain.
You told me you hate massages.
"Buy stamps,
pick up dry cleaning...
don't let Phoebe in."
I can't believe this.
How long has this been going on?
Well, uh, Alexandra is...
Oh, it has a name.
Phoebe, don't get upset.
Okay. Oop, too late.
I'm leaving.
Come on, Chandler,
let's go.
Well, Pheeb, I thought I...
Yeah, what the hell.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Oh, okay, okay, come on,
one more push, one more push.
Oh!
Come on, honey,
we're almost there,
almost there.
Oh, Joey, I'm so happy
things worked out for us
and we're having
this baby together.
I love you so much.
Oh, I love you, too.
And I hope it's not
an inappropriate
time to say this
but you're the best
sex I've ever had.
Oh, that's always appropriate.
Oh, okay, okay, come on.
One more push, one more push.
( grunting )
WOMAN:
There we go. Oh...
Here is your
beautiful baby.
Congratulations.
Aw...
( crying like a baby )
( sobs )
I hope you are a better father
than you are a friend!
( bawling )
( gasping )
Oh! Ooh!
( knock at door )
Joey. Joey.
What-what's going on?
Come feel this,
come feel my belly.
Uh...
Joey, the baby
is kicking for the first time.
Will you please come
and feel this?
Really?
Yes.
You know what,
maybe, uh, you...
Maybe you should come to me.
I'm not wearing any bottom,
so...
Oh. Okay.
Oh, my, oh, my God.
Oh! Oh, it's unbelievable.
Well, she is kicking so much.
Oh, she's like, um...
Oh, who's that kind of
annoying girl soccer player?
Mia Hamm.
Mia Hamm!
Wow, it's amazing.
Oh, whoa! One hand
on the sheet, Joey.
Hey! Oh, sorry.
Hey, babe.
Hey, honey.
So we just got a wedding gift
from Bob and Faye Bing.
They don't like us, do they?
Who says you can't get a nice
punch bowl for under six bucks?
Maybe we can take it back.
No, it doesn't say
where it came from.
Where would we return it?
How about to the street?
Say, from the balcony?
Why don't we just
find a place for it?
( grunts )
How about in that cabinet?
No. That's where we
keep the canned goods.
Have you completely
forgotten everything
you learned at
orientation...?
How about the closet
by the bathroom?
Oh, okay.
Why don't you
let me do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
I will do it.
Honey, you have to learn
to sit down and relax
and let your husband
take care of things
once in a while.
It's locked.
You have to help me.
Why is it locked?
No reason. I-I-I keep
private things in there.
Well, you know, I've been
living here for a while
and I've never seen
what's inside that closet.
What is in there?
Feminine stuff.
Don't try to make
me uncomfortable
with feminine stuff!
Chandler, there is nothing
in there that concerns you.
If you love me, you'll just...
you'll let it go.
Fine.
Thank you.
Love you.
Hi, Chandler.
Lovely day, huh?
You.
Phoebe, if it helps,
Alexandra's only
been massaging Monica
for, like, three years.
"If." I said if it helps.
Why won't you
let me massage you?
Well, it's... I mean, I was
just... I'd be self-conscious.
I mean, you're my friend;
I'd be naked.
Monica, we lived together
for years.
I've seen you naked.
That's different.
We were roommates, and when?
I'm curious
about the human body.
Hey, come on, Phoebe
you can understand why
this would be weird for me.
But I'm a professional,
and I'm really good.
Look, if you're uncomfortable,
we can stop.
Just give me a chance, okay,
please?
Okay, if it means
that much to you.
It does.
How would you feel if you
couldn't share your cooking?
Or imagine how Ross would feel
if he couldn't teach us
about dragons.
Dinosaurs.
Potato, "potahto."
Hey.
Hey, Ross.
The baby's kicking.
Wh... It is?
It's not kicking right now.
Although we would love
to see you do that again!
When-when was
it kicking?
What happened?
Last night. I just felt it,
then I went into Joey's room
and he was sleeping...
A dreamless sleep.
My God, the baby is kicking.
That's great.
Although I kind of wish
I would have been there
to feel the kicking for
the first time, you know.
Well, I've got some stuff
going on in here
if you want to feel it.
Look, I don't want
to miss any more baby stuff
so here, here's my new
pager number, okay?
Anytime anything
pregnancy-related happens, use
it.
I'll be there, okay?
I don't care if it's
3:00 in the morning
and all you want
is some ice cream.
Wow. Can I get a copy of that?
Phoebe:
Are you under the sheet?
Yes.
Great. Let's begin.
How's the pressure?
Ah... it's nice.
Well, Phoebe,
you are good.
Stating the obvious,
but thank you.
And it's not weird, is it?
No.
Oh...
That's right,
you just enjoy.
Oh...
Oh, yeah!
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, God, Phoebe!
Oh, that's it!
That's it, right there!
Oh!
Oh-ooh...
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Oh...
( door closes )
I wasn't trying
to open your closet!
I wasn't trying to open
your closet, I swear!
Wow, Monica runs a pretty tight
ship around here, doesn't she?
What are you doing?
Monica has a secret closet
and she won't let me
see what's in it.
Why not?
I don't know!
What could she possibly
be hiding in here
that I can't see?
I don't know.
Ooh...
I'll bet it's Richard.
Why would Monica
be keeping Richard in here?
Well, off the top
of my head, uh...
maybe she's having her cake
and eating it, too--
you being the cake,
Richard being the too.
Or...
And here we go.
I saw this movie once
where there was a door
and nobody knew
what was behind it.
And when they finally
got it open, millions
and millions and millions
of bugs came pouring out
and they feasted
on human flesh.
You know, it wouldn't kill you
to respect your wife's privacy!
Stupid closet full of bugs, man.
Joey...
Joey, something feels weird
and not "good weird."
I don't know... Whoa!
Do not worry, okay?
When my sisters were pregnant
they got every weird
feeling in the book.
It was always nothing.
Really?
Absolutely.
But we're going to stop by the
hospital just to be sure, okay?
I'll page Ross on the way.
Okay. Oh, God,
ow, ooh!
O-okay, Rach,
Rach look at me.
Look at me.
Everything's going to be fine.
Okay.
Trust me, okay?
Come on.
Take my hand.
Here we go.
I've got, ow,
crushing bones!
Okay, good thing we're
going to the hospital.
Hey. So?
She's fine.
She was experiencing
Braxton-Hicks contractions--
mild discomfort
caused by contractions
in the uterine wall.
Hmm. Mild
Discomfort?
So I take it you've had one
of these Braxton thingies?
So, so...
But everything is normal?
DOCTOR:
Absolutely.
No.
And there's no danger
to her or the baby?
Contractions can be unnerving
if you don't know what they are
but she's fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
Aw... thank you for
being so nice and calm.
Calm? I wasn't calm.
I'd never been more scared
in my entire life!
But wait, you just said
everything was going to be okay.
What do I know?
I'm not a doctor.
But it, oh, but everything
is okay; I'm fine.
You sure?
Yes, yes.
I got half a mind to contract
that doctor's uterus, though.
"Mild discomfort"?
What is he talking about?
Is everything okay?
Oh, hey, hey.
Yeah, everything is fine.
Your page said "Come
to the hospital."
What, what was it?
What happened?
Something called
Braxton-Hicks contraction.
Oh. Oh. Thank God.
That's no big deal.
Most women don't
even feel them.
Okay, no uterus,
no opinion.
Hey, uh, what's
with the candy?
Oh, when you beeped me,
I was on the line
at the concession stand
at the movie theater.
Oh, you went to the
movies by yourself?
No-- Mona!
Oh, I got to go back
in there.
Why? What's wrong?
Everything's fine.
I just got to go back there.
No, really, tell me,
wh-what's up?
( whispering ):
I-I forgot my underwear.
So, thanks so much for-for
bringing her to the hospital.
Oh, hey,
don't worry about it, man.
Don't worry about it.
No big deal.
Yeah, but still, I mean,
it should have been me.
I'm the dad.
If you have any questions
here's some information
on Braxton-Hicks.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, and by the way, you did the
right thing by bringing her in.
You're going to make
a wonderful father.
Oh, uh...
Hey, not as good
as this guy.
He brought Twizzlers.
There's got
to be a way!
Easy there,
Captain Kirk.
Oh, do you have a bobby pin?
Yeah.
Oh, no, wait.
I'm not a nine-year-old girl.
Then why do you throw like one?
Maybe Monica has a bobby pin.
Oh, sure, "Monica."
So, how's the hideously
inappropriate crush
on Rachel coming?
Really good, really good, yeah.
I should be ready
to kill myself any day now.
You sure found that quick.
I wish I didn't feel
this way about Rachel anymore.
I wish things could
go back to normal.
I mean, I love
living with her
and helping out
with the baby
is just amazing
but now I think Ross
feels left out, you know?
When I had to take Rachel
to the hospital
the doctor thought
I was the father.
God, you should have seen
the look on Ross's face.
By the way, I have no idea
what I'm doing here.
For all I know,
I'm just locking it more.
Oh, hey, did you try
opening it with a credit card?
That's a good idea.
So, Ross is kind
of bummed, huh?
( sighs )
I feel terrible.
It's not your fault.
What are you going to do
not take her to the hospital,
you know?
You're doing nothing wrong...
except for harboring an
all-consuming love
for the woman
that's carrying his baby.
Richard, if you're in there
could you pass me
my credit card?
Hey.
I got to tell you,
yesterday was amazing.
That massage felt so good.
No, I got that.
So, what do you say
we make it a weekly
appointment?
Okay. You should know, though
I've raised my rates
to $200 an hour.
Oh, okay.
I mean $500.
What?
$600.
What's going on?
You make sex noises
when you get massaged.
Yeah, and it
really freaked me out
and after a while
I even tried to hurt you
and it just spurred you on.
What? You're crazy.
There's nothing sexual
about the noises I make.
Really, there's nothing
sexual about this?
Oh! Oh, God!
Oh-oh-oh!
What are you looking at?
I mean, hi.
This is so embarrassing.
Oh, my God, I'm never going
to get massaged again.
No, you can't let this
stop your from getting massages.
Look, I have lots
of clients that make
the same noise as you do.
Really?
Well, not clients, lovers.
Let's just... You know,
we'll try it again.
Come back
and we'll work through it.
You sure?
Yes.
I guess.
Great.
Okay, now if you'll
just excuse me.
So, did you hear
something you liked?
Hey, Ross, check it out.
I learned a new trick, huh?
Hey. I brought
you some lunch.
Oh, that's
so sweet of you.
Eh.
Oh, yum.
( garbled ):
Did you put pickles on this?
Well, yeah.
Oh, Ross!
What? What?
Rach, what?
What's going on?
I made her favorite,
tuna sandwich with pickle.
Pickle? Pickle
makes her sick.
Giving her pickles
is like giving me salad.
I'm sorry, Rach.
I didn't know.
Are you going to be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
But can someone make sure
that sandwich is gone
when I get out there?
I'm on it!
I can't believe this.
I shouldn't be the one
making her throw up.
Relax, Ross,
it could happen to anyone.
Yeah? Not to you
'cause you know
this stuff.
I don't know any of it
and I'm the father.
I wish I was more involved,
you know?
( groans )
Well, if anyone is keeping score
I no longer eat tuna.
Hey, can I talk to you guys
for a second?
Yeah.
What's up?
Sit down.
I want to talk
about our situation.
Are you breaking up
with us?
The thing is...
because I live with Rachel
I'm here for a lot of the stuff
and Ross...
Ross is missing everything.
So...
Yeah?
Maybe you two should live
together.
Are you asking me
to move out?
You don't want me here?
No, no, I love living with you.
It just seems that...
if you're going
to have a roommate
it might as well be the father.
But, Joey, I don't think
Ross wants me
to move into his apartment
and disrupt his life like that.
Or he does.
Well, I would love
to be around
for you and the baby
and we can just try it,
like, on a temporary basis.
But, Ross,
it's you and me.
So? Sure.
But it wouldn't be
anything romantic
and I'm dating Mona.
Damn it! Mona!
I was supposed to meet her,
like, an hour ago.
What is wrong with me?
So, what do you think?
I don't know
Is it crazy?
No, no.
Joey, this is a smart idea.
Well, I was due.
Okay, let's do it.
I'll move in.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, Rach, that's great.
That's great.
( cooing )
Not too shabby.
I got this all off myself...
using my wife's tools.
Oh, my God!
( gasps )
How did you get
in there?!
( goofy laugh )
You're messy.
No! You weren't
supposed to see this!
I married Fred Sanford!
No, Chandler,
you don't understand.
( hums Sanford and Son theme)
Okay, okay, fine.
Now you know, okay?
I'm sick.
No, honey,
you're not sick.
Look, I don't love you
because you're organized.
I love you
in spite of that.
Really?
You promise
you won't tell anyone?
Yes.
Look, now that I know
if I've got some
extra stuff lying around
can we share the closet?
Oh, well, it's just, um...
I'm afraid
you might mess it up.
Hey.
What's up?
Rachel's all moved out, huh?
How you taking it?
I want to have a few beers,
but I got rid of those
because Rachel couldn't stand
the smell of them.
So, I've thrown back
a lot of orange juice
with calcium, though.
And it's a couple weeks past
its expiration date
so it's got a bit of a kick.
Are you okay?
You kidding me?
I'm great.
Yeah, I'm better
than great. I am good.
And now that she's gone
I can do all this stuff
around there
that I couldn't do before,
you know?
Like, um, I can walk
around naked again, you know?
I can watch porn
in the living room
right?
This is good for me, you know?
I like being on my own.
I'm better off this way.
I'm a lone wolf, a loner.
Alone.
All alone...
forever.
What's a wolf got to do
to get a hug around here?!
Oh!
That's it.
Just relax.
Oh! Oh-oh!
Come on. More.
Oh, God!
You like that, don't you?
Yeah, right there.
You want it there,
you take it there, baby.
Uh, Phoebe?
Yeah, say my name.
Say it.
And now I'm going
to cover you back up
and won't be speaking
with you for several weeks.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org